{"id":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","title":"Conjugação","questions":[{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"gosto","id":"rhdrrd93gwgjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"0ilamtfqiwpnjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"gostas","id":"zpqmw4gv5ssjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ah88amh4ascjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"gosta","id":"hpanqmt1anjjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"jxaawky1gbcjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"gostamos","id":"njth1i1909jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"tnog9w917mcjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"gostais","id":"u1t7f5qhrp9jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"0kssgwn636ajgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aimer - gostar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"gostam","id":"g2ecyi7z3ljgl5p0qh"}],"id":"sr0z3yjp9ohjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"gostei","id":"xx7ksokdczjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"s21t1mlj2hjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"gostaste","id":"fshgkx784tvjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"bn3m91gbelejgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"gostou","id":"42943vqd2osjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"f3hhz3as2qujgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"gostamos","id":"rhwbdi9in18jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"xa0mf39gstkjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"gostastes","id":"ujhp09ooxtjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"cntarz9j8yqjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aimer - gostar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"gostaram","id":"0bl07ndi4czbjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"90j5bqb8ejwjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"gostarei","id":"90owmyytourjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"mty83cb5nmmjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"gostaras","id":"ncsfm1tja1gjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"t9mmdx3g7bjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"gostara","id":"jwhmlfy1p5jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"j4xnlgo48u8jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"gostaramos","id":"lzn2vyw2d6jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"occrh4zjlzjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"gostarais","id":"pvleoudowlbjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"kz5r5xyzpwpjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aimer - gostar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"gostarão","id":"jeyt8imt5cjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"5z84tap7y39jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"chego","id":"22pcf35dt06jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"iu4qn4ku9tjjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"chegas","id":"jalgui54afejgl5p0qh"}],"id":"rtw51peh12jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"chega","id":"v0m9mgxmd3qjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"6l6tf1wsuoajgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"chegamos","id":"cdxo3qz5ymjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"fduzn4omytejgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"chegais","id":"adff11g6b6mjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"v2lcw0rpo09jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - arriver - chegar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"chegam","id":"exd3h1x5zpejgl5p0qh"}],"id":"sojokp2pbjjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"chegei","id":"97m1rqa1k15jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"y04bv7eyqjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"chegaste","id":"1xb9eqoq696jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ukc533k6osjjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"chegou","id":"g9rwd4jtridjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"v65x0juqyc9jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"chegamos","id":"qvfjq6ywrhjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"6xingb4109cjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"chegastes","id":"ln5fbdnvvyjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"b1e1tqdgddnjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - arriver - chegar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"cheragam","id":"ztagvel93bmjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"zdyfjincgjjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"chegarei","id":"37ovi4ztldjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"2f3swy1uwb6jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"chegaras","id":"7cww8ueaoz6jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"7a07600oekvjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"chegara","id":"twva2xp502jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"btudj9nx96jgl5p0qh","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"chegaremos","id":"zlhz5pev0jljgl5p0qh"}],"id":"d5moqn50rejgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"chegarais","id":"tthzkea3mopjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"txtku7024kbjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - arriver - chegar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"chegarāo","id":"913c1n2oln8jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"tpni3x5fwojgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"tenho","id":"ul4xgbd8j9jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"elbp30h8nydjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"tens","id":"ulpfyr7pr1jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"l41xezbvy6jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"tem","id":"1xorm0dph3njgl5p0qh"}],"id":"58cyjwi22mujgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"temos","id":"d4gcxzudnfajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"c6akr2mjfiqjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"tendes","id":"11xlt7dsgeljgl5p0qh"}],"id":"l8cliekqcbfjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - avoir - ter","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"têm","id":"vdsimnfwccjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"9j000ljhd55jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"tive","id":"20tlj9zpscajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"m7pvdlcsuajgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"tiveste","id":"7vq2pjznoagjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"qsiai2ejozfjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"teve","id":"ibn2ukwmlkijgl5p0qh"}],"id":"m4k58g1oammjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"tivemos","id":"s02oegg0czjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"w1z1slutg9jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"tivestes","id":"9o43ljxy5cmjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"9qzjobh0rl7jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - avoir - ter","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"tiveram","id":"wphqaj8hqfajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"99a57m6x44ujgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"terei","id":"ukjhqx9zqedjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"yw98zpzqmjgjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"teras","id":"0vbcuhkm3cujgl5p0qh"}],"id":"o07rwpyvcjejgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"tera","id":"4cmzmso0ghkjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"i0o75rsfdssjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"teremos","id":"kemb0olji5qjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"q8qorxwa6tjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"tereis","id":"o9c3szgnqijgl5p0qh"}],"id":"4ecw8d86yxjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - avoir - ter","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"terāo","id":"3200unz4njajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"z26uals13wjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"digou","id":"43xfb6ej3jqjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"tu5d2a4m7kkjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"dizes","id":"a09o6mx0xkmjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"fggwtttzz6hjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"diz","id":"74ygmik2nv5jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"d503ff3rh0qjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"dizemos","id":"paugn7qby6jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ows44dw0axjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"dizeis","id":"0k2ps6r8qysajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"dsfsu3x1junjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - dire - dizer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"dizem","id":"illwrbal75bjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"noe1r5hrkjjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"disse","id":"rrwohdi2kpdjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ubd13atw6sjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"disseste","id":"34dgtuj0jyujgl5p0qh"}],"id":"6t8o4hpc1rojgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"disse","id":"4abf73mefc2jgl5p0qh"}],"id":"33tmorzw7xjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"dissemos","id":"3izaxz479cojgl5p0qh"}],"id":"mjow0kbggdpjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"dissestes","id":"g5uup6li3xljgl5p0qh"}],"id":"mymnxcyknksjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - dire - dizer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"disseram","id":"ul1w0i37yrsjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"eejplzgnaa5jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"direi","id":"85lwg8a03sjjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ors7gtsgq8jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"diras","id":"jx9ec73k9vjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"60boc006rvgjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"dira","id":"auadp6osg7cjgl5p0qh"}],"id":"w0c7phuu8ijgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"diremos","id":"zelcfom6nxejgl5p0qh"}],"id":"ngsoak2g3qgjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"direis","id":"4gobe8cnkjojgl5p0qh"}],"id":"8qj6r1plpbrjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"futur - dire - dizer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"dirāo","id":"wdcsxik64ajgl5p0qh"}],"id":"jmyz48nuq9bjgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"estou","id":"9el3k9vpf66jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"3zozslh59w8jgl5p0qh"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"estas","id":"1utafbccw9jjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"0nqsvvhhicujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"esta","id":"fx1nmrcgpkjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ioeqdm9bd4ljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"estamos","id":"fhyp4jxkwbgjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"h6g8x8burakjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"estais","id":"e8zkoapd61ajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"z3sy5n96fhjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - estar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"estao","id":"9t9fh8a6tajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"5xmsmb9cs34jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"estive","id":"howr5yvoxfnjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"e0kpeqo6zmbjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"estiveste","id":"uo335mxhzvojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"s178u6afl3djgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"esteve","id":"hkkluv5xnijgl5p0qi"}],"id":"n0n4b3qk2qbjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"estevemos","id":"hogq1kzrvz8jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ff8jw2wk0xjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"estevestes","id":"zomwzy2lpzjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"flhv9v55mecjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - estar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"estiveram","id":"3gq7sdiregjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"hmht2hewg3wjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"estarei","id":"jlzdzvxlp7jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wg54c6e8c0pjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"estaras","id":"gxls9hhv2bdjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"br86brtdoutjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"estra","id":"z5dxvv6q4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xnrr4xvqnfnjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"estaremos","id":"zn7d01xl0whjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"gcp27kq60ynjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"estareis","id":"lnfefucgpxejgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xilvlw9uvejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - estar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"estarāo","id":"di035qkgalljgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8itrlzg56lyjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"faço","id":"5kcxf3jshp4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"sji3n8nxjksjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"fazes","id":"80ljyeyqlf8jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"vhq4auhc7bjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"faz","id":"ec28utqebu6jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"1mr88xpbs8jjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"fazemos","id":"gcbrxbat1gcjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ljbbupt3lmjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"fazeis","id":"htvocc9a4qjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"elim2jvd2isjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - faire - fazer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"fazem","id":"gvuksy2bl3jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"f9dj62lhlcmjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"fiz","id":"3dwabsdz6fijgl5p0qi"}],"id":"te45j5b771jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"fizeste","id":"0kyi0yf1fr1cjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xwvc09igorjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"fez","id":"8htu13f7nbmjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"a0buuv42hrkjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"fizemos","id":"72mkckeaoonjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"rzz44h1pl0ojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"fizestes","id":"4s4uuujedc4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"i77yd0sv8ljjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - faire - fazer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"fizeram","id":"72fgf1cdzg7jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"w3346biti3ijgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"farei","id":"kxx37vfwp3jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"r3tw18xumwjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"faras","id":"vzec42763jgjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"tlijht8s6trjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"fara","id":"uzclp7t17cnjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"gxj1ukd9p3ljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"faremos","id":"l06j882ib8mjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"w6tbz3k012jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"fareis","id":"bu7m1vztervjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"5eznpfdv4ixjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - faire - fazer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"farao","id":"ojzqmfvwahhjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"gfdu3m4ub5jjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"sei","id":"04vp6bx4xnmojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"4huihynx0ewjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"sabes","id":"dyd5jvtbv88jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"hrv36qqryjljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"sabe","id":"xjhacjdmiyjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"zx2bqs66hshjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"sabemos","id":"nyzfglyknajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wqagblq4awljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"sabeis","id":"fbm5le9ktxnjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"iv8b7fpkd1pjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - saber - savoir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"sabem","id":"2k0yqsnkpyrjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"c6lkg0t7wrqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"soube","id":"stanudi8ryjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"vnr05793gujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"soubeste","id":"tdke1pydoobjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"heav6xm12qjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"soube","id":"4tyea0kypocjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"yyg9scgyoi9jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"soubemos","id":"gcmk0dk4fjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"1kkjd1rtukjjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"soubeis","id":"dgqsy2snq7ujgl5p0qi"}],"id":"rgu6rxsrpcjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - saber - savoir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"souberam","id":"51wrpgki4wejgl5p0qi"}],"id":"yi9yeexc3anjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"saberei","id":"kq9s434rr3kjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"z8bzozuzhfijgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"saberas","id":"pids1mcz5ipjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"4x465xf7tzmjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"sabera","id":"u3lcxg90mkjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"lz0eufyrg8djgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"saberemos","id":"s6fvcmla26ajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"54sxptt31lqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"sabereis","id":"nhoobhn0jcpjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"l7cgtclc51jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - saber - savoir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"saberāo","id":"y96u6ipyawjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ozt97ifqgbjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"venho","id":"lt7w34826vjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"0cn0bkbfprgwjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"vens","id":"ebd1prhdkf5jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"zy6k24ms4ejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"vem","id":"0l775g5s75whjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"pniz3wappcjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"vimos","id":"76ahlrt0yoxjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"guac6z9fzyjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vindes","id":"aksc39tqu5njgl5p0qi"}],"id":"20nwtru2ykqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - venir - vir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"vem","id":"vnl5mkigy8gjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"gbszus2nldjjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"vim","id":"rpdmjznhjkhjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"yl4ysp12pyhjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"vieste","id":"kw75zko4kfjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"q4foucn7bxejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"veio","id":"syrw7q8ur9jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2ni4yiyl6jxjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"viemos","id":"dseaa7zaekvjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"mglfv77h4lqjgl5p0qi","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vestes","id":"y3hruj878fjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8torvkfjzzyjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - venir - vir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"veiram","id":"2hpg1kw57y7jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"mfdjeaykj1jjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"virei","id":"55629pneiyjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8bsvhkk5l9djgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"viras","id":"iymq6ig552jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"dxz3up8zj9gjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"vira","id":"akqc15xir3vjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"aavdarf48ocjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"viremos","id":"78tt2f5d6i3jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"irvh8r87388jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vireis","id":"r8cq0aizz8kjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"zh4ov5v3xmgjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - venir - vir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"virāo","id":"15wq7olw75jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ijk9qwxsyvtjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"dou","id":"0vgk1bvzkzzejgl5p0qi"}],"id":"t4worzfhgxjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"das","id":"zsk72oba6ygjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"93mpwgn1ct6jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"da","id":"kfn6igxhcaajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"kumdue4fcfqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"damos","id":"92n6uk3g6ibjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"q8hc0uswrbejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"dais","id":"1n0rirw4lr2jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"4zvp3xzl3fxjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - donner - dar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"dāo","id":"z99duyyi8sjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"9tjjuwhxphfjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"dei","id":"ysdtufoi5fpjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xtf3s6lbhhjjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"deste","id":"h9q8fqaagsgjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8fy6njwvlr3jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"deu","id":"iyvp53s5s9ljgl5p0qi"}],"id":"3hzy6xc3mppjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"demos","id":"dbxp8lm3fjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"fu8kqc6am0hjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"destes","id":"q19a1w5zvzqjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"mzzq1wz5zhmjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - donner - dar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"deram","id":"dlib676l9eajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wj3hc922axnjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"darei","id":"xjpur9uznljgl5p0qi"}],"id":"bikfyjqk22jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"daras","id":"868ub8xk4xqjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"6b71kx2ynkxjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"dara","id":"ai8qvfclanljgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ob78hfqbhxojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"daremos","id":"e5xx6folhg9jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"lbak0pwmnrnjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"dareis","id":"4421wx8u122jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"0qocy7z0opkjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - donner - dar","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"darāo","id":"9d25su780r7jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2g7bc4y52czjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"quero","id":"pamv2wohrsmjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wynhint9rujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"queres","id":"2vn7598yhy4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"06i0xnd2bkbjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"quer","id":"nnrpnwlh3ykjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"x9s5759qb7jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"queremos","id":"2bv2kioe5qhjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"sqeq6n77n1qjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"quereis","id":"9s094t0zmltjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"c7zqk2qo67ujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - vouloir - querer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"querem","id":"c76a1q42vlqjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"0ak2fa6xfwddjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"quis","id":"zps6auo6qbnjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"jn7fs9cdiwjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"quisiste","id":"5fke8mohiitjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"93u1g0j5kqajgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"quis","id":"3wj8y3cbtgcjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"vio56ih7hekjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"quisemos","id":"auvxn0on3fojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"95zgy8w9lskjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"quisestes","id":"xahwjcn0mjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"j02wu6xxybjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - vouloir - querer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"quiseram","id":"eb809k0044ojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"30bcnvc9xbhjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"quererei","id":"8rwyjo1yopvjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"h5vpr6gfhoqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"quereras","id":"b61x265bq49jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"gf2xd52s6ejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"querera","id":"tntq6yk4ojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"j24wa66qrjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"quereremos","id":"6vo61luu693jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"opx1bceie2ijgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"querereis","id":"324n8m4vmljgl5p0qi"}],"id":"7nm47kcvzerjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - vouloir - querer","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"quererao","id":"4bovl03g015jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"izzrqcx2pyjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"vou","id":"djjvgyi7b79jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"haxxbmik0eljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"vais","id":"pu3i76o81gjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"tto165eoe5jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"va","id":"0gxzhez5wlrjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"76at0217bo4jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"vamos","id":"6t7g17pq2djgl5p0qi"}],"id":"5xbl5egquiejgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"ides","id":"03p8s7wsbbpajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2z4j7b1saltjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - aller - ir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"vão","id":"elj3jgz776jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"kzldqvkj8hgjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"fui","id":"otlc4z7hs4jjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"c9y8pnkeenjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"foste","id":"907344preu6jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"234iufmjltwjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"foi","id":"9uu4siyy0njgl5p0qi"}],"id":"uwp4xarwdkjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"fomos","id":"rhx6h6cd66djgl5p0qi"}],"id":"kvmbbehjhhfjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"fostes","id":"psda6b6bnjkjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"r34zko9uqdjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - aller - ir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"foram","id":"2sgvhpog736jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"znjads2zb7fjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"irei","id":"j9vdhj0ycqrjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"x1m4np7m2zqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"iras","id":"wdbt1g4bqwjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8pvomukqsqcjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"ira","id":"9ckd88huxnijgl5p0qi"}],"id":"dsgij9p8tngjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"iremos","id":"x0xfcwtv0edjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wrscjghcichjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"ireis","id":"j8wieehwkxjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"5s6vkc17hjljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - aller - ir","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"irao","id":"1yokq26rqbjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"j8uk534vd9jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"vejo","id":"9uvdwiesta4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xhiwoejhvojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"ves","id":"ifuymx6jy6jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"28akixkg1yqjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"vê","id":"gmb3au2to3wjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"abkqejpvpz8jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"vemos","id":"kp0jfba65gjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"x1f4ge16gtjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vedes","id":"72uhstwfxtvjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2q40xfjjqxcjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - voir - ver","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"vêem","id":"kgm9i4o565ijgl5p0qi"}],"id":"febrqn54obijgl5p0qi","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"vi","id":"q174h8z1p6pjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"1iv88xw8ygljgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"viste","id":"rxqwo8d0qfjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"qwa0qsqh0emjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"viu","id":"879k86gs02fjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"vbhx0mziy5njgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"vimos","id":"kfvd07d6mqdjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"pzwcurvbjmjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vistes","id":"ozak97f7fojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2iglk54d0xjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - voir - ver","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"viram","id":"b2alkanjrt4jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xkij4t0az5qjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"verei","id":"x555i8wkhekjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"58hpanj6weujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"viras","id":"4baynw2rwkjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ru1dxs6aqx8jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"vira","id":"04yl32ainzy9jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"a2vh06qmksrjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"viremos","id":"svij8kuwymjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"1mplcxwiosjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"vereis","id":"z4hlkbmbkzsjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"n79dozl35tjgl5p0qi","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"futur - voir - ver","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"verao","id":"pgqlpvpxcxrjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"8fgwrtk80txjgl5p0qi","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"posso","id":"amttmfu12thjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"3acqx82u4t5jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"podes","id":"7nqzqk54pbfjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2v55zph99mpjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"pode","id":"uma1jed4lcjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"l75q7v16xjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"podemos","id":"rskl8mtjgwgjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"z4dsy38npujgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"podeis","id":"f6mhzy9qm2ajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2pg130jcb6rjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - pouvoir - poder","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"podem","id":"ezyf5p44e9ojgl5p0qi"}],"id":"9r1dedrmbgjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"pude","id":"g6pa1hx38xcjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"fgogqzvemfojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"pudeste","id":"3ib9l8a7rrpjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"9d8pb09vszjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"pude","id":"5b8lhxjph1qjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"g70fizpizx5jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"pudemos","id":"ta5sk68wu8jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"rv9sp3e7fhjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"pudestes","id":"6pg786ulikjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"aiw3opeczxojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - pouvoir - poder","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"puderam","id":"c7en114m1ajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"xpolp2s6fzjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"poderei","id":"2y1hpjkozhjjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"wy4sbd6416ijgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"poderas","id":"keedsyv1j5jgl5p0qi"}],"id":"3etmq1dq7cojgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"poderá","id":"mxo2b8hrkajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"5hjfaergdk9jgl5p0qi","questionnaireTitle":"Conjugação","questionnaireId":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh","questionnaireType":"questionnaire","foundType":"answer"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"poderemos","id":"bty7j1l2rajgl5p0qi"}],"id":"ieneyjsae6jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"podereis","id":"z3p7wogbspkjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"yoxuu3pvodjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"futur - pouvoir - poder","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"poderao","id":"vmk0eq52x5djgl5p0qi"}],"id":"2xtig5r0aqcjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"sou","id":"58zng8xzz0ujgl5p0qi"}],"id":"10k9edpos93jgl5p0qi","favorite":false},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"es","id":"cwcd7iookrhjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"osqb7voj5hrjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"é","id":"5g65ertlcldjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"7g315uaajy5jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"somos","id":"e37bd6e8e1njgl5p0qi"}],"id":"pnkxkygfi1jgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"sois","id":"x0cr9kkohxjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"48q6b818ucjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"présent - être - ser","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"sāo","id":"uduy1xf03apjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"grlmjczrr4cjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"fui","id":"tqekep58hbqjgl5p0qi"}],"id":"id8dd1yyoytjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"foste","id":"4oa8cnws677jgl5p0qj"}],"id":"wzap8hoqnqbjgl5p0qi"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"ele/ela","answers":[{"answer":"foi","id":"t7twjvrf8aijgl5p0qj"}],"id":"qqefdtyl12jgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"fomos","id":"j7feoeys3ojgl5p0qj"}],"id":"cpb22ku321ojgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"fostes","id":"kejokcor6fjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"ubsjunqrpnpjgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"prétérit - être - ser","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"foram","id":"79ijnyjdtwhjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"qst79cb6v9jgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"eu","answers":[{"answer":"serei","id":"q9gc3tscjmjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"cslvi44gondjgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"tu","answers":[{"answer":"seras","id":"ej280yem8qtjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"vv6fd3m29unjgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"ele","answers":[{"answer":"sera","id":"hya6582tpk4jgl5p0qj"}],"id":"71l9t5yzq9ajgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"nos","answers":[{"answer":"seremos","id":"9cko5h4g7k8jgl5p0qj"}],"id":"dkgms9xbbnwjgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"vos","answers":[{"answer":"sereis","id":"r5ufgnt77iqjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"cwf2jx2vqm5jgl5p0qj"},{"questionLabel":"futur - être - ser","question":"eles/elas","answers":[{"answer":"serao","id":"fa8dq9b2gcgjgl5p0qj"}],"id":"dv9bz95fl5jgl5p0qj"}],"creationDate":"2018-04-29 18:36:30","modificationDate":"2018-05-02 15:39:06","type":"questionnaire","showGroup":true,"fileName":"ii0thusnsojgl5p0qh.json","favoriteQuestions":false}